Preliminary Inventory to the University of Chicago. Office of Public Relations. Records 1925-1985
University of Chicago Library
University of Chicago. Office of Public Relations. Records.
1925-1985
2010-067
23.5 linear feet (19 boxes)
Hanna Holborn Gray Special Collections Research Center University of Chicago Library 1100 East 57th Street Chicago, Illinois 60637 U.S.A.
This collection includes press releases and news clippings from the University of Chicago Public Relations Office. Boxes 1-13 contain bound volumes of all University press releases in quarterly volumes. Boxes 14-19 contain folders of unbound press releases and are organized in folders by departments.
Information on Use
Access
The collection is open for research.
Related Resources
Browse finding aids by topic.
INVENTORY
- Press Releases: January-March, 1944 (Box 1)
- Press Releases: April-June, 1944 (Box 1)
- Press Releases: July-September, 1944 (Box 1)
- Press Releases: October-December, 1944 (Box 1)
- Press Releases: January-March, 1945 (Box 1)
- Press Releases: April-June, 1945 (Box 1)
- Press Releases: July-September, 1945 (Box 2)
- Press Releases: October-December, 1945 (Box 2)
- Press Releases: January-March, 1946 (Box 2)
- Press Releases: April-June, 1946 (Box 2)
- Press Releases: July-September, 1946 (Box 2)
- Press Releases: October-December and Sports Index and Releases January-December, 1946 (Box 2)
- Press Releases: January-March, 1947 (Box 2)
- Press Releases: April-June, 1947 (Box 3)
- Press Releases: July-September, 1947 (Box 3)
- Press Releases: October-December, 1947 (Box 3)
- Press Releases: January-March, 1948 (Box 3)
- Press Releases: April-May, 1948 (Box 3)
- Press Releases: July-September, 1948 (Box 4)
- Press Releases: October-December, 1948 (Box 4)
- Press Releases: January-March, 1949 (Box 4)
- Press Releases: April-June, 1949 (Box 4)
- Press Releases: July-September, 1949 (Box 5)
- Press Releases: October-December, 1949 (Box 5)
- Press Releases: January-March, 1950 (Box 5)
- Press Releases: April-June, 1950 (Box 5)
- Press Releases: July-September, 1950 (Box 6)
- Press Releases: October-December, 1950 (Box 6)
- Press Releases: January-March, 1951 (Box 6)
- Press Releases: April-June, 1951 (Box 6)
- Press Releases: July-September, 1951 (Box 6)
- Press Releases: October-December, 1951 (Box 6)
- Press Releases: January-March, 1952 (Box 7)
- Press Releases: April-June, 1952 (Box 7)
- Press Releases: July-September, 1952 (Box 7)
- Press Releases: October-December, 1952 (Box 7)
- Press Releases: January-March, 1953 (Box 7)
- Press Releases: April-June, 1953 (Box 7)
- Press Releases: July-December, 1953 (Box 8)
- Press Releases: January-March (Index), 1954 (Box 8)
- Press Releases: April-June, 1954 (Box 8)
- Press Releases: July-December, 1954 (Box 8)
- Press Releases: January-March (Index), 1955 (Box 8)
- Press Releases: April-June, 1955 (Box 8)
- Press Releases: July-December, 1955 (Box 9)
- Press Releases: January-May (Index), 1956 (Box 9)
- Press Releases: June-December, 1956 (Box 9)
- Press Releases: January-June (Index), 1957 (Box 9)
- Press Releases: July-December, 1957 (Box 9)
- Press Releases: January-June (Index), 1958 (Box 10)
- Press Releases: July-December, 1958 (Box 10)
- Press Releases: January-June (Index), 1959 (Box 10)
- Press Releases: July-December, 1959 (Box 10)
- Press Releases: January-March, (Index) 1961 (Box 11)
- Press Releases: April-June, (Index) 1961 (Box 11)
- Press Releases: July-September (Index), 1961 (Box 11)
- Press Releases: October-December (Index), 1961 (Box 11)
- Press Releases: January-March (Index), 1962 (Box 12)
- Press Releases: April-June (Index), 1962 (Box 12)
- Press Releases: July-December (Index), 1962 (Box 12)
- Press Releases: January-March (Index), 1963 (Box 12)
- Press Releases: January-June, 1960 (Box 13)
- Press Releases: July-December, 1960 (Box 13)
- Press Relations Conference on World Tensions May 1960 (Box 13)
- Handwritten Notebook Index of Press Releases, 1925-1926 (Box 14)
- Handwritten Notebook Index of General and Sports Releases, 1927-1929 (Box 14)
- Typed Index of Press Releases, 1927-1929 (Box 14)
- Release Index of General and Sports, 1930-1932 (Box 14)
- Release Index of General and Sports, 1933-1935 (Box 14)
- Department of Press Relations Press Releases, 1937-1938 (Box 14)
- Department of Press Relations Press Releases, 1940-1942 (Box 14)
- Office of Press Relations Press Releases, Commencement News Clippings, 1942-1946 (Box 14)
- Office of Press Relations Press Releases, 1947-1949 (Box 14)
- Department of Press Relations Press Releases, 1940-1941 (Box 14)
- Department of Press Relations Press Releases, 1942 (Box 15)
- Press Releases (Languages), 1937-1938 (Box 15)
- Press Releases (Languages), 1939-1941 (Box 15)
- Press Releases (Divinity), 1937-1941 (Box 15)
- Press Releases (Economics), 1937-1939 (Box 15)
- Press Releases (Economics/Divinity), 1940-1941 (Box 15)
- Press Releases (Education), 1936-1939 (Box 15)
- Press Releases (Faculty Honors and Science), 1931-1955 (Box 15)
- Press Releases (Feature), 1940-1946 (Box 15)
- Press Releases (Feature), 1945-1948 (Box 16)
- Press Releases (Music), 1938-1943 (Box 16)
- Press Releases (Medicine), 1937-1941 (Box 16)
- Press Releases (Libraries and Education), 1935-1941 (Box 16)
- Press Releases (Law), 1937-1941 (Box 16)
- Press Releases (History), 1934-1939 (Box 16)
- Press Releases (Geology, Geography, Paleontology), 1934-1941 (Box 16)
- Press Releases (Gifts), 1936-1939 (Box 16)
- Press Releases (Gifts), 1940-1945 (Box 17)
- Press Releases (Oriental Institute), 1934-1938 (Box 17)
- Press Releases (Oriental Institute), 1939 (Box 17)
- Press Releases (Oriental Institute), 1939-1941 (Box 17)
- Press Releases (Divinity), 1937-1941 (Box 17)
- Press Releases (Physics), 1936-1941 (Box 17)
- Press Releases (Physiology), 1937-1941 (Box 17)
- Press Releases (Political Science), 1937-1941 (Box 18)
- Press Releases (Psychology), 1937-1941 (Box 18)
- Press Releases (Sociology), 1939-1942 (Box 18)
- Press Releases (Summer Quarter), 1942-1952 (Box 18)
- Press Releases (Tuition), 1945-1949 (Box 18)
- Press Releases (Education), 1939-1941 (Box 18)
- Press Releases (Faculty). 1941-1950 (Box 18)
- Press Releases (Graduate School of Business), 1958-1976 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Graduate School of Business, Institute of Professional Accounting), 1962-1976 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Graduate School of Business), 1957-1972 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Graduate School of Business), 1965-1981 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Department of Biophysics, Division of Biological Sciences, Biomedical Careers Conference), 1964-1975 (Box 19)
- Press Releases ( Book store, Bursar, Community and Family Study Center, Comptroller, Institute for Computer Research, Sickle Cell Center), 1958-1985 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (College), 1965-1978 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Center for Urban Studies), 1964-1970 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Chemistry), 1969-1978 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Center for Studies in Criminal Justice), 1965-1984 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (University Court Theatre), 1968-1978 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Center for the Study of Welfare Policy), 1969-1974 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (China, Centers, Synchronocyclotron), 1957-1975 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Various), 1959-1979 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Various), 1958-1982 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Various), 1961-1985 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Various: E-G), 1955-1976 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Divinity School), 1960-1978 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Drug Abuse, Deans, Diabetes), 1962-1983 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Education), 1962-1978 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Enrico Fermi, football), 1955-1980 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Economics, exchange program, fees), 1957-1979 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (English), 1958-1975 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Geography, Geophysical Sciences), 1957-1982 (Box 19)
- Press Releases (Library), 1951-1980 (Box 19)